Inventory to the Annelise Graebner Anderson Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Office of Management and Budget, 1981-1983 (Box 28-139)
  - Memorandum for proposed PD re Treasury Exchange Stabilization (Box-folder 129: 17)
  - Status of appeals to the budget review board – December 9, 1981 (Box-folder 129: 18)
  - Footnotes – special edition – April 14, 1981 (Box-folder 129: 19)
  - Retirement party invitation for George E. Hall (Box-folder 129: 20)
  - Sensitivity of the budget to economic assumptions (Box-folder 129: 21)
  - Budget outlook (Box-folder 129: 22)
  - Talking points on the economy – February 1982 (Box-folder 129: 23)
  - Statement of David A. Stockman – February 10, 1982 (Box-folder 129: 24)
  - Presentation of the Honorable David A. Stockman – February 17, 1982 (Box-folder 129: 25)
  - Last distribution of the OMB reconciliation tables (Box-folder 129: 26)
  - Gramm-Latta II Revisions (Box-folder 129: 27)
  - Identification of extraneous provisions in the reconciliation bill (Box-folder 129: 28)
  - Correction to Daily Reconciliation Tables – June 17, 1981 (Box-folder 130: 1)
  - Program division submissions of “Questionable Reconciliation Items in House Committee Bill” (Box-folder 130: 2)
  - Selected House Markup and Floor Action Calendar for Legislative Affairs (Box-folder 130: 3)
  - Weekly Reconciliation Report – June 12, 1981 (Box-folder 130: 4)
  - First-final version of reconciliation table (Box-folder 130: 5)
  - Senate-Passed Reconciliation Savings (Box-folder 130: 6)
  - Gramm-Latta II Savings Estimates (Box-folder 130: 7)
  - Summary of Senate Authorizing Committee Reconciliation Recommendations – June 15, 1981 (Box-folder 130: 8)
  - Substitute Reconciliation Bill Savings (Box-folder 130: 9)
  - Reconciliation Tables (Box-folder 130: 10-11)
  - Final Gramm-Latta II proposal estimates (Box-folder 130: 12)
  - GL II-JTGM (Box-folder 130: 13)
  - Status of budget appeals – December 16, 1981 (Box-folder 130: 14)
  - Comparison of agency employment (FTE) requests with targets – FY ‘83 and ‘84 (Box-folder 130: 15)
  - Sale Federal Asset USA survey (Box-folder 130: 16)
  - User Changes (Box-folder 130: 17)
  - Information related to the reconciliation act (Box-folder 130: 18)
  - TCH’s contributions to the 82 cuts exercise (Box-folder 130: 19)
  - Receipts and user fees (Box-folder 130: 20)
  - Accounts to be excluded from the “pro rata” tabulation to be made by BRD (Box-folder 130: 21)
  - Copies of TCH contribution to identifying inappropriate levels of personnel in certain activities (Box-folder 130: 22)
  - Potential Fees, User Charges, and Reimbursements (Box-folder 130: 23)
  - Feasibility of personnel reductions (Box-folder 130: 24)
  - Administration, house, and senate totals (Box-folder 130: 25)
  - Urgent supplementals (Box-folder 130: 26)
  - Senate Budget Committee Reconciliation Directive (Box-folder 130: 27)
  - Legislative Cost-Savers in the 1982 Budget as revised (Box-folder 131: 1)
  - Administration and Senate outlay totals for 1982 (Box-folder 131: 2)
  - Authorizations in reconciliation that are below the budget (Box-folder 131: 3)
  - Program, DOT Policy and Evaluation (Box-folder 131: 4)
  - Status report for administration-sponsored “cost-saver” legislation-97th congress, 1st session (Box-folder 131: 5)
  - Senate floor action on Reconciliation bill (Box-folder 131: 6)
  - Comments on proposal on GAO proposals unpaid taxes (Box-folder 131: 7)
  - House Budget Committee items (Box-folder 131: 8)
  - Description of the SBC reconciliation directive by function and a table showing the policy changes from the administration by function for 1982 and 1983 (Box-folder 131: 9)
  - House Budget Committee Suggestions for Budget Reductions through Administrative Practices (Box-folder 131: 10)
  - Anticipated major legislative initiatives – 97th congress (Box-folder 131: 11)
  - Listing of suggestions for inclusions in the Reconciliation Bill (Box-folder 131: 12)
  - Details of proposals for the fiscal year 1981 and 1982 (Box-folder 131: 13)
  - House Budget Committee: Markup of Budget Resolution (Box-folder 131: 14)
  - House/Senate Budget Committee Action (Box-folder 131: 15)
  - Trouble Spots on Meeting Promises on Legislation (Box-folder 131: 16)
  - Commitments to Tip O ‘Neil on Administration Legislation (Box-folder 131: 17)
  - The Gramm-Latta Substitute (Box-folder 131: 18)
  - Remarks by Chairman Leslie Kanuk, federal maritime commission before the international association of NVOCC’S Miami, Florida (Box-folder 131: 19)
  - Draft memo to president on 1981 outlay reductions (Box-folder 131: 20)
  - Current House and Senate Budget Committee Outlay Totals for 1982 (Box-folder 131: 21)
  - First Resolution for 1982 (Box-folder 131: 22)
  - “Most Frequently Asked Questions” compilation on the President’s Program for Economic Recovery (Box-folder 131: 23)
  - House Republican Leadership Meeting – February 24, 1982 (Box-folder 131: 24)
  - Hollings + Phil Gramm alternative budget reduction proposals for FY83 (Box-folder 131: 25)
  - House committee: Agriculture – June 11, 1981 (Box-folder 131: 26)
  - Response to charges against Gramm-Latta – July 15, 1981 (Box-folder 131: 27)
  - Checklist of GL II Contents – June 9, 1981 (Box-folder 131: 28)
  - Outline for GL-II – June 16, 1981 (Box-folder 131: 29)
  - House Committee: Public Works and Transportation – June 11, 1981 (Box-folder 131: 30)
  - Congressional Budget Alternatives Working Draft (Box-folder 131: 31)
  - Reactions to the President’s FY83 Budget (Box-folder 131: 32)
  - Memorandum on proposals for possible consideration during efforts to construct a bipartisan agreement for achieving increased control of federal spending and federal deficits (Box-folder 131: 33)
  - Congressional Testimony (Box-folder 131: 34)
  - Budget proposals – Gramm IV (Box-folder 131: 35)
  - National Association of Manufacturers – March 19, 1982 (Box-folder 131: 36)
  - OMB staff estimates of outlay savings from various cost-of-living adjustments (COLA) proposals (Box-folder 131: 37)
  - “Gypsy Moth” testimony before the House Budget Committee on Tuesday, March 30, 1982 (Box-folder 131: 38)
  - Contributions relating to the Presidential briefing – February 16, 1982 (Box-folder 131: 39)
  - Information Paper #6: The Total Budget (Box-folder 132: 1)
  - The Dramatic Increases in 1980 and 1981 Outlays (Box-folder 132: 2)
  - Budget Outlook (Box-folder 132: 3)
  - Memorandums relating to reports from Mike Hudson (Box-folder 132: 4)
  - Memorandum of a report from House Appropriations – subcommittee on commerce, state, justice and the judiciary (Box-folder 132: 5)
  - Comparison tables of economic assumptions (Box-folder 132: 6)
  - Possible Unprinted Amendments (Box-folder 132: 7)
  - Memorandum to DAS from SEH (Box-folder 132: 8)
  - Notes from Laurie Howard regarding action in the DOT subcommittees (Box-folder 132: 9)
  - Notes from Dee Wilson regarding house appropriation subcommittee action (Box-folder 132: 10)
  - Thrift Industry notes (Box-folder 132: 11)
  - Letters from David A. Stockman regarding the thrift assistance legislation (Box-folder 132: 12)
  - Letters from David A. Stockman regarding the Administration’s strong opposition to H.R. 6267, the “Net Worth Guarantee Act” (Box-folder 132: 13)
  - Thrifts (Box-folder 132: 14)
  - TRIS (Box-folder 132: 15)
  - 1982 tracking (Box-folder 132: 16)
  - 1981 tracking (Box-folder 132: 17)
  - National Airport Policy (Box-folder 132: 18)
  - Weekly Reports (Box-folder 132: 19)
  - Gas Tax Conference Bill (Box-folder 132: 20)
  - User Fees (Box-folder 132: 21)
  - Letter from E. Patrick McGuire regarding the conference board (Box-folder 132: 22)
  - Senate Budget Committee-S. Con. Res. 9 Revising the second budget resolution for FY 1981 to include reconciliation – March 16, 1981 (Box-folder 132: 23)
  - Memorandum regarding rescission clock (Box-folder 132: 24)
  - Administration-sponsored legislation 97th congress, 1st session – March 19, 1981 (Box-folder 132: 25)
  - The Conference Board (Box-folder 132: 26)
  - The Dramatic Increases in 1980 and 1981 Outlays (Box-folder 132: 27)
  - White House Meeting – March 24, 1981 (Box-folder 132: 28)
  - Senate Committee on Veterans Affairs (Box-folder 132: 29)
  - Note from Robert C. Byrd regarding the budget outlook (Box-folder 132: 30)
  - HBC and SBC Function Totals 1982 (Box-folder 132: 31)
  - Differences between the House Budget Committee Approved Resolution and the Bi-Partisan Substitute (Box-folder 132: 32)
  - Comparison of the Administration and Bipartisan Substitute Budget Proposals (Box-folder 132: 33)
  - 1981 Supplemental and rescission bill (Box-folder 132: 34)
  - Senate Floor Consideration of Reconciliation Instructions (Box-folder 132: 35)
  - Tables listing the difference of the Senate Budget Committee reports and the President’s proposals (Box-folder 132: 36)
  - Possible Unprinted Amendments (Box-folder 132: 37)
  - Banking Committee-Urban Mass Transit (Box-folder 132: 38)
  - Basic Guidance from DAS on position on floor amendments to the reconciliation bill (Box-folder 132: 39)
  - Memorandum regarding guidance on administration position on Gramm-Latta and the specific changes in Gramm-Latta (Box-folder 132: 40)
  - Material for response to congressmen O’Neill and Jim Wright (Box-folder 132: 41)
  - Senator Chaffee (Box-folder 132: 42)
  - Senate Budget Committee Mark-Up (Box-folder 132: 43)
  - Cumulative Report on Rescissions and Deferrals (Box-folder 132: 44)
  - Transmitting Legislation to the Hill (Box-folder 132: 45)
  - Charts – Carter January Budget (Box-folder 132: 46)
  - Senate Committee on Veterans Affairs (Box-folder 132: 47)
  - Senate Select Committee on Small Business (Box-folder 132: 48)
  - Senate Committee on Labor and Human Resources (Box-folder 132: 49)
  - Senate Committee on the Judiciary (Box-folder 133: 1)
  - Senate Committee on Governmental Affairs (Box-folder 133: 2)
  - Senate Committee on Foreign Relations (Box-folder 133: 3)
  - Programs included in the social services consolidation (Box-folder 133: 4)
  - Senate Finance Committee (Box-folder 133: 5)
  - Legislation to support the 1982 budget as revised (Box-folder 133: 6)
  - Status Report for Administration-Sponsored “Cost-Saver” Legislation 97th Congress, 1st Session (Box-folder 133: 7)
  - Administration-sponsored legislation 97th congress, 1st session – March 19, 1981 (Box-folder 133: 8)
  - Alternative 1982 subsidized housing program reductions (Box-folder 133: 9)
  - “Draconian cut from 83-86” exercise for TCH (Box-folder 133: 10)
  - Estimates of the potential impact of the Reconciliation Act (Box-folder 133: 11)
  - The Reagan Block Grant Proposals and Congressional Revisions (Box-folder 133: 12)
  - Senate Finance Committee (Box-folder 133: 13)
  - Senate Committee on Environment and Public Works (Box-folder 133: 14)
  - Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources (Box-folder 133: 15)
  - Senate Committee on Commerce, Science, and Transportation (Box-folder 133: 16)
  - Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs (Box-folder 133: 17)
  - Senate Committee on Armed Services (Box-folder 133: 18)
  - Senate Committee on Agriculture, Nutrition, and Forestry (Box-folder 133: 19)
  - Senate Budget Committee – Background Materials – March 16, 1981 (Box-folder 133: 20)
  - Three memoranda done by BRD on the Senate Budget Committee’s markup on the reconciliation instructions and the CBO estimates of the revised 1982 budget (Box-folder 133: 21)
  - Mike Hudson’s comments on the progress of the Senate Budget Committee mark-up of S. Con Res. 9 (Box-folder 133: 22)
  - Effect of the Omnibus Reconciliation Act on GSA’s Stockpile Sales (Box-folder 133: 23)
  - Rough Draft of estimates of employment in special purpose staff offices who are engaged in certain functions (Box-folder 133: 24)
  - Percentage change in 1982 BA for Accounts excepted from Prorata (Box-folder 133: 25)
  - Major forms of Federal Property Asserts (Box-folder 133: 26)
  - User changes collected by receipt accounts (Box-folder 133: 27)
  - Employment reductions – TCH (Box-folder 133: 28)
  - Employment (Box-folder 133: 29)
  - 1983-1986 BA Cuts-small Business Administration (Box-folder 133: 30)
  - Agencies (Box-folder 133: 31)
  - Note on DAD’s and PADS and AD’s for budget and federal personnel (Box-folder 133: 32)
  - Memorandum/notes regarding Domenici plan—and guidance (Box-folder 133: 33)
  - Carter Budget/Reagan Change/Reagan Budget Decisions (Box-folder 133: 34)
  - Addendum: Revenue and expense for operating major power revolving funds (Box-folder 133: 35)
  - Foreign military sales trust fund (Box-folder 133: 36)
  - Additional detail on federal funds sale of government property except for strategic reserve (Box-folder 133: 37)
  - Additional detail on proceeds from federal funds sale of power and other utilities (Box-folder 133: 38)
  - Additional detail of collections from federal funds sales of agriculture, mineral, and other land products (Box-folder 133: 39)
  - Additional detail on “other rents” (Box-folder 133: 40)
  - Additional details for “other permits and licenses” (Box-folder 133: 41)
  - 1983 Budget Decisions-Department: Justice (Box-folder 133: 42)
  - Legislative Problems Report (Box-folder 133: 43)
  - Operations in Event of Expiration of Continuing Resolution (Box-folder 133: 44)
  - Daily OMB legislative highlights report (Box-folder 133: 45)
  - 1983 Subsidized Housing Programs Appropriation – House Appropriations Subcommittee Action (Box-folder 133: 46)
  - Comparative Statement of New Budget (Obligational) Authority (Box-folder 133: 47)
  - 1983 Senate Appropriations Bill (Box-folder 133: 48)
  - Commerce, Justice, and State appropriation bill notes (Box-folder 133: 49)
  - Daily OMB Legislative Highlights Report (Box-folder 133: 50)
  - Outstanding letters, talking points and positions – December 1982 (Box-folder 133: 51)
  - Justice department has experienced sustained growth in staffing and resources (Box-folder 133: 52)
  - Effect of the proposed increase in the gas tax and other highway use taxes on fiscal year receipts (Box-folder 133: 53)
  - S. 2607 – Housing and Community Development Amendments of 1982 (Box-folder 133: 54)
  - Talking points on the further continuing appropriations resolution, 1983 (Box-folder 133: 55)
  - Revised appropriations tracking fact sheets for both budget authority and outlays (Box-folder 133: 56)
  - Justice budget (Box-folder 134: 1)
  - President’s Private Sector Survey (Box-folder 134: 2)
  - Additional material on the justice appeal requested by the Director (Box-folder 134: 3)
  - Appropriations Tracking Fact Sheet – 1st 1983 budget resolution (Box-folder 134: 4)
  - Proposed letter and supporting papers on the DC bill (Box-folder 134: 5)
  - Draft of the commerce-justice-state letter (Box-folder 134: 6)
  - 2nd continuing resolution, 1983 – house appropriation committee mark-up (Box-folder 134: 7)
  - Draft letter and position statement on the D.C. appropriations bill (Box-folder 134: 8)
  - Talking points on Gonzalez II (Box-folder 134: 9)
  - Amendment to H.J. Resolution 631 Modified Housing Certificates (Box-folder 134: 10)
  - Calendar and summary tables reflecting congressional action on appropriation bills (Box-folder 134: 11)
  - H.J. Res. 631 Senate Committee Changes in Funding (Box-folder 134: 12)
  - 1983 Second Continuing Resolution – December 16, 1982 (Box-folder 134: 13)
  - Job Stimulus Bill Budget Authority (Box-folder 134: 14)
  - Ten domestic bills FY 1983 appropriations – continuing resolution (Box-folder 134: 15)
  - Summary of Pending Appropriation Bills House Action (Box-folder 134: 16)
  - Administration’s concerns with the Senate Committee recommendation on the Commerce, Justice, State, and the Judiciary Appropriation Bill, 1983 (S. 2956) (Box-folder 134: 17)
  - Talking Points – Labor/HHS/Education – Appropriation Bill (Box-folder 134: 18)
  - Appropriations tracking fact sheet- 1st 1983 budget resolution- treasury, postal service, general government appropriation bill, 1983 (Box-folder 134: 19)
  - Appropriations tracking fact sheet- 1st 1983 budget resolution- transportation and related agencies appropriation bill, 1983 (Box-folder 134: 20)
  - Talking points- Department of Defense appropriation bill, 1983 S. 2951 (Box-folder 134: 21)
  - Reconciliation mark-up/house merchant marine and fisheries committee (Box-folder 134: 22)
  - Letters/position statements on pending appropriation bills (Box-folder 134: 23)
  - Talking points- Commerce/state/justice-appropriation-bill (Box-folder 134: 24)
  - I. Justice department has experienced sustained growth in staffing and resources (Box-folder 134: 25)
  - Justice Appeal Papers (Box-folder 134: 26)
  - 97th Congress 2d Session-House of Representatives-Report No. 97-959 –- Further Continuing Appropriations, 1983 (Box-folder 134: 27)
  - Senate Republican Committee Assignments in the 98th Congress (Box-folder 134: 28)
  - TCH Review of the CR report (Box-folder 134: 29)
  - Enrolled Bill H.R. 7019 – Transportation and Related Agencies Appropriation Bill, 1983 (Box-folder 134: 30)
  - Highlights of Conference Action H.J. Res. 631 – December 19, 1982 (Box-folder 134: 31)
  - Signing statement on continuing resolution (Box-folder 134: 32)
  - Talking points on the lame duck session (Box-folder 134: 33)
  - Daily legislative highlights report – November 15, 1982 (Box-folder 134: 34)
  - Creation of a “Drug Czar” (Box-folder 134: 35)
  - Senior staff Inquiry Regarding Pay Raise (Box-folder 134: 36)
  - Pending Enrolled Bills – December 21, 1982 (Box-folder 134: 37)
  - Enrolled H.J. Res 631 –- Continuing Appropriations for Fiscal Year 1983- Sponsor: Rep. Whitten (D), Mississippi (Box-folder 134: 38)
  - Letter regarding the Miller amendment (Box-folder 134: 39)
  - Legislative problems report (Box-folder 134: 40)
  - Summary of Congressional action on FY 1983 appropriations to date (Box-folder 134: 41)
  - President’s last day in parenthesis (Box-folder 134: 42)
  - HUD legislative proposals that would limit the applicability of Davis-Bacon Requirements (Box-folder 134: 43)
  - Proposal for speed up of cash flow for custom duties (Box-folder 134: 44)
  - Treasury’s legislative proposal to institute a system of user fees for the customs service (Box-folder 134: 45)
  - 1983 Budget Appeal – Immigration and Naturalization Service (Box-folder 135: 1)
  - Ed Meese’s Speech November 19 to the American Society of Criminology (Box-folder 135: 2)
  - Department of Justice 1983 Budget Appeal Summary (Box-folder 135: 3)
  - 1983 Budget Appeal Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box-folder 135: 4)
  - Comments regarding the proposal on the FY 1983 budget request (Box-folder 135: 5)
  - Department of justice appeal (Box-folder 135: 6)
  - Economic conditions (Box-folder 135: 7)
  - Financial markets update (Box-folder 135: 8)
  - Earthquake reinsurance proposal submitted by the American international group (Box-folder 135: 9)
  - Drug abuse fact sheet (Box-folder 135: 10)
  - Organized crime/drug initiative (Box-folder 135: 11)
  - Federal-district relations (Box-folder 135: 12)
  - District of Columbia (Box-folder 135: 13)
  - D.C. Bond Legislation (Box-folder 135: 14)
  - Termination of D.C. new hires under the civil service retirement system (CSRS) after December 31, 1983 (Box-folder 135: 15)
  - Meeting concerning INS detention center and BoP prison issues (Box-folder 135: 16)
  - Detention center (Box-folder 135: 17)
  - Deregulation (Box-folder 135: 18)
  - DOD (Box-folder 135: 19)
  - DEA (Box-folder 135: 20)
  - Agenda and background papers for the next meeting of the Cabinet Council on Economic Affairs, 6/18/ at 8:45 A.M. in the Roosevelt room (Box-folder 135: 21)
  - Entitlement Advisory Group Public Assistance Subgroup (Box-folder 135: 22)
  - Appropriations tracking fact sheet 1st 1983 budget resolution – treasury, postal service, general government appropriation bill, 1983 (Box-folder 135: 23)
  - Talking points – commerce/state/justice-appropriations-bill (Box-folder 135: 24)
  - Appropriations tracking fact sheet 1st 1983 budget resolution energy/water development (Box-folder 135: 25)
  - Annually funded discretionary programs summary of pending bills (Box-folder 135: 26)
  - 1983 Senate Appropriations Bill (Box-folder 135: 27)
  - 1983 Defense Appropriation Bill – House Subcommittee (Box-folder 135: 28)
  - Lame Duck (Box-folder 135: 29-31)
  - USPS (Box-folder 135: 32)
  - NOAA (Box-folder 135: 33)
  - Transportation appropriation bill (Box-folder 135: 34)
  - Letter from William French Smith regarding budget proposals (Box-folder 136: 1)
  - First 1983 budget resolution-comparison of house and senate 302 (A) and 302 (B) allocations and the president’s budget (Box-folder 136: 2)
  - Congressional action on 1983 appropriation bills (Box-folder 136: 3)
  - Senate appropriations committee status: FY 1983 (Box-folder 136: 4)
  - Major differences between house and senate action for conference committee-agriculture and rural committee (Box-folder 136: 5)
  - H.R. 7205: Labor/HHS/Education appropriation bill, 1983 (Box-folder 136: 6)
  - Analysis and Stanton Alternative to Gonzalez Bill HR 6296 – the House Banking Committee Housing Bill (Box-folder 136: 7)
  - Talking points on Gonzalez II (Box-folder 136: 8)
  - Budget resolution comparison table-selected HUD programs – December 14, 1982 (Box-folder 136: 9)
  - Commerce-justice-state appropriations bill (Box-folder 136: 10)
  - Legislative problems report (Box-folder 136: 11)
  - Chronological – January 21 – April 20, 1981 (Box-folder 136: 12-13)
  - Chronological – April 21 – June 30, 1981 (Box-folder 136: 14-16)
  - Chronological – July 1 – September 30, 1981 (Box-folder 136: 17)
  - Chronological – July 1 – September 30, 1981 (Box-folder 137: 1)
  - Chronological – October 1 – December 31, 1981 (Box-folder 137: 2-3)
  - National Consumer Cooperative Bank Briefing Materials (Box-folder 137: 4-5)
  - Status of Remaining Administration Legislation (Box-folder 137: 6)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 137: 7)
  - Notes on appropriations (Box-folder 137: 8)
  - Status of Budget Revisions – March 19, 1981 (Box-folder 137: 9)
  - Memorandum regarding DPA III Authorities (Box-folder 137: 10)
  - Memorandum regarding damage control (Box-folder 137: 11)
  - Pending enrolled bills – December 15, 1982 (Box-folder 137: 12)
  - H.R. 6296 Housing and Urban Rural Recovery Act of 1982 (Box-folder 137: 13)
  - Justice Department Red Herrings (Box-folder 137: 14)
  - U.S. Attorneys (Box-folder 137: 15)
  - Department of Justice 1983 Budget Appeal Summary (Total FTE) (Box-folder 137: 16)
  - Crime and Justice – Capital Punishment – Nation’s Largest Police Organization Endorses Governor Ronald Reagan (Box-folder 137: 17)
  - 1983 Budget Appeal – Federal Bureau of Investigation (Box-folder 137: 18)
  - Flash item – House floor action on Treasury/Postal Appropriations bill (Box-folder 137: 19)
  - Objectionable language provisions in appropriations bills (Box-folder 137: 20)
  - H.R. 5133 – The Fair Practices in Automotive Products Act (Box-folder 137: 21)
  - Fact Sheet on Second 1983 Continuing Resolution – December 9, 1982 (Box-folder 137: 22)
  - Bailout Legislation (Box-folder 137: 23)
  - Materials to Support the Revised 1982 Budget – Amendment to March 5th Memo (Box-folder 137: 24)
  - SBC Decisions (Box-folder 137: 25)
  - Letter from William French Smith regarding a department’s budget (Box-folder 137: 26)
  - FY 1985 Spring Review Block Grants (Box-folder 137: 27)
  - Bill Positions (Box-folder 138: 1-3)
  - 1985 Budget Spring Review – Student Aid and UI/TAA (Box-folder 138: 4)
  - Friday Night Money Supply/Credit Market Report – December 17, 1982 (Box-folder 138: 5)
  - Tentative house floor schedule for December 13-?? As of 12/10: 1:30 P.M. (Box-folder 138: 6)
  - Miscellaneous notes (Box-folder 138: 7)